louisberger.com 2019-04-17

# Privacy Policy | Louis Berger

We welcome you to The Berger Group Holdings, Inc. website. We ask that you review this Privacy Policy, which is intended to constitute a binding license agreement that conditions your use of this site ("Agreement"). Our goal is to protect our rights in order to provide you with access to the free content available at this site. If you do not wish to be bound by this Agreement after you have read it, please leave the site. If you remain on this site, or return thereafter, you agree to be bound by this Agreement.

## Information Collected and Stored Automatically

When you visit this page we automatically collect and store only the following information:  
1\. Your Internet address.  
2\. The date and time you access our site.  
3\. The pages you visit.  
4\. The location from which you access the site.  
5\. The type of operating system you use.  
We use this information to help us make our site more useful to visitors, to learn about the number of visitors to our site, to ensure that this service remains available to all users, and to identify unauthorized attempts to change information or otherwise cause damage.

## Personal Information

Louis Berger welcomes the EU General Data Protection Policy (GDPR) as a chance to enhance our commitment to data protection and to only collect your personal data where it is necessary. Good data practice is about trust. Here at Louis Berger, we value the trust you place in us to handle your personal data. As such, we will continue to work hard at maintaining an ethical and transparent data privacy culture that ensures your data is protected. We encourage you to learn more on this topic by reading **Louis Berger’s Data Privacy Policy**. To learn more about Louis Berger’s compliance with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework, we invite you to read the **Privacy Statement for Louis Berger U.S. Entities**.

## Website Security

For website security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, The Berger Group Holdings, Inc. utilizes a computer system that employs software to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage. Any attempts to cause damage or unauthorized access to confidential data could be subject to legal action.

This Privacy Policy was last amended in May 2018.
